I tried the new and improved link extraction code,
لقد جرّبت استخدام كود استخراج الرابط الجديد والمحسّن،
on this article about Yoshiharu Yamaguchi.
في هذا المقال عن يوشيهارو ياماغوشي.
I expected the extraction code to find this link to Osaka, but instead,
لقد توقعت أن يعثر كود الاستخراج على هذا الرابط إلى مدينة أوساكا، لكن بدلًا من ذلك،
it found this little question mark which is actually a link
لقد عثر على علامة التعجب الصغيرة هذه والتي هي في الواقع رابط
to the Wikipedia page about Japanese character sets.
لصفحة على موقع Wikipedia لمجموعة من الأحرف اليابانية.
Technically, BeautifulSoup found the right link.
لقد عثرت حزمة BeautifulSoup على الرابط الصحيح تقنيًا.
But once again, this is not what I really want.
لكن مجددًا، هذا ليس ما أريده حقًا.
The same behavior can lead to other bugs too.
يمكن أن تؤدي الطريقة نفسها إلى بعض الأخطاء الأخرى أيضًا.
If the first link in the article is a link to a footnote or a citation for example,
إذا كان الرابط الأول في المقال هو رابط لحاشية سفلية أو اقتباس على سبيل المثال،
that's what the link extractor will find.
فإن هذا ما سيجده مستخرج الرابط.
What we really want to do though,
ومع ذلك، إنما نريد فعله حقًا،
is to find what first link that's to an ordinary Wikipedia article,
هو العثور على الرابط الأول للانتقال إلى مقالة Wikipedia العادية،
not to a help page. How can we do that?
وليس إلى صفحة مساعدة. كيف يمكننا القيام بذلك؟